<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="schema/schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
    <!--Goes in Belgium not France-->
    <letter xml:id="Brussels-1955-07-26">
        <figure>
            <graphic url="images/July26.jpg"/>
            <caption>July 26th letter: front</caption> 
        </figure>
        <dateLine><date when="1955-07-26"> July 26, 1955</date></dateLine>
        <placeName>Brussels</placeName>

        <front>
            <readers>Dear People:</readers>
            <p n="1">We are just about to take off for <placeName>Copenhagen</placeName> and are sit- ting
                around so I will try to send this second installment of our trip report. If I
                remember correctly, the last letter came from the boat. We arrived in
                    <placeName>Cherbourg</placeName> and got safely on the <transport>train</transport> to
                find that it was over 90. We nearly died on the ride to <placeName>Paris</placeName>. Very
                unairconditioned train and blazing sun. The first thing we did when we arrived at
                    <placeName>Le Bristol</placeName> was fall in cold tub. We went out for
                    dinner later and cele- brated with Cherries Jubilee. Very tasty! The next day <persName>Mrs. Behrend</persName> hired a
                    <transport>car</transport> and guide and we drove all over <placeName>Paris</placeName>.
                It is so beautiful but so expensive<x rw="?">!</x>
                <fade>$</fade>90 a minute to breath! We did a bit of shopping, had lunch in the
                    <placeName>Bois de Boulougne</placeName> shopped on the Left Bank, got
                    <transport>train</transport> tickets and that night went to the <placeName>Casino de
                    Paris</placeName>. Pretty naked ladies I must say. We were not carried away by it
                but did see it, so that is that.</p>
            <p n="2">The next morning we were up at the crack of dawn and off to <placeName>Tours</placeName>. The man and
                his wife who ran the <placeName>Manoir Bercheron</placeName>, where we stayed as a
                    m<misspelling word="member"/>m<eSpace i="extra space"/>ber of the family were terribly nice. We
                arravied in time for lunch and then got in a little car and went
                through some beautiful country to see some of the chateaux. We enjoyed it
                traemndously. You can see where the old French painters get all their inspirations.
                Lovely rivers, old mills and beautiful trees. That night after dinner we
                went to a nearby chateau, <placeName>Azay-le-Rideau</placeName> which was illuminated. Just like fairyland.
                They also had a sort of play very cleverly done just done with voices and lighting
                which told the history of the building. We will never forget it.</p>
            <p n="3">Thursday, <persName>the Davidsons</persName>, our hosts and their little boy and and
                ourselves went on another chateaux trip which was just a grand as the day before. We
                had a picnic on the way and <x><corr ori="day"><hand>tea</hand></corr></x> on the way home. Great
                fun. The only thing that marred the trip was another guest who arrived who knew all
                about everything and told it in the loudest of voices. I got in a ter- rible row
                with him about sports. Everyone was on my side but you couldn't get a word in edge
                wise. Itwas rather funny to look back on but I nearly had a nervous breakdown when
                it was going on.</p>

            <p n="4">
                Friday we left <placeName>Tours</placeName> at about eleven and got back in <placeName>Paris</placeName> for
                    lunch. After the lovely meal we changed out on foot to do some
                shopping.</p>
          
        </front>
        <figure>
            <graphic url="images/July26Back.jpg"/>
            <caption>July 26th letter: back</caption>
        </figure>
        <back>
         
            <p n="4">and walked around. This we did. Not too many purchases. We were going up to
                    <placeName>Montmartre</placeName> but decided to get to bed early to leave for
                    <placeName>Brussels</placeName> the next day.</p>
            <p n="5">We had a perfect flight from <placeName>London</placeName> here. <persName>Mercedes Bucher</persName> met us
                at the airport and we came to the hotel. <persName>The Wilsons</persName>, <persName>Mrs. BB’s cousin</persName>, called and
                came over for a drink. We then went for a delicious lunch, food is
                marvelous here, on the <placeName>Grand Place</placeName> which is fantastic. Mercedes has a
                    <transport>car</transport> so we spent the afternoon seeing
                    <placeName>Brussels</placeName> which is very pretty. Lovely parks and old buildings. Had
                    dinner in a very old place with lots of atmoshpere and good food.
                    Sunday we piled into the <transport>car</transport> and went to
                    <placeName>Bruges</placeName>, about and hour and a half away. A divine old town. We
                took a ride in a <transport>carriage</transport> all over the town. Great fun. On
                the way back we stopped for tea in the <placeName>Ostend</placeName> which is
                a big seaside resort. Arrived back here at eight and had a light supper
                on the <placeName>Grand Place</placeName> which is illuminated at night and breathtaking.
                Yesterday we shopped most of the day and walked around seeing things. All had
                    cocktails at the <placeName>Wilsons hotel</placeName> and dinner
                later.</p>
            <p n="9"> It is now Tuesday again and we leave here at 12:55 for
                    <placeName>Copen-hagen</placeName> arriving there at <time>4:30</time>. Have to change
                planes in <placeName>Amsterdam</placeName>. Mer-cedes will pick us up in a few minutes so I will stop and go pay the bill etc. 
                The <persName>Wilsons</persName> left a while ago for <placeName>Paris</placeName>. 
                We will see them in <placeName>London</placeName> in August.</p>
            <p n="10">We see by the paper that it is still unbearable in <placeName>New York</placeName> and
                are pleased to be here. Weather has been perfect except for the day we arrived.</p>


             <p>Much love to all from both of us.</p>
            <p><hand><persName>Gail</persName></hand></p>
            
            <p><hand>Dear Lou—</hand></p>
            <p><hand>Thanks for your letter in <placeName>Paris</placeName>— Sorry your golf fell apart—It’s fun anyway— Shall be
            anxious to see the new addition. Will you call <persName>Mary Bartol</persName> and tell her to get the time
                for the <persName>Wheeler</persName> thing. Tell her to tell <persName>Betty Ewing</persName> too
                for me— Also call <persName>Sophie</persName>— on 8-03 &amp;1 and tell her same thing. Having a lovely trip.</hand></p>
            <p><hand>Much love—</hand></p>
            <p><hand><persName>G—</persName></hand></p>
        </back>
    </letter>
    
</xml>
