<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="schema/schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
    <letter xml:id="Brussels-1955-07-23">
        <figure>
            <graphic url="images/July23.jpg"/>
            <caption>July 23rd</caption>
        </figure>
        <dateLine><date when="1955-07-23">Saturday July 23rd.</date></dateLine>
        <p>Now we leave Paris- not very much of a visit but there is much to see in Europe- and many places we may never get around to again<eSpace i="forgot period but made extra space"/>  However, Paris I hope to visit agai<x>en</x>.</p>
        <p>We Left <placeName>Le Bristol</placeName> for the <placeName>Air<hand rw="way">ras</hand></placeName> a little before 9 and  Stopped enroute at <persName>Hermes</persName> to collect a scarf-decorated with add the famous chateaux of <placeName>France</placeName>- a few of which we <hand>HAS</hand> visited during our recent little stay in Tours. This scarf a souv<hand>i</hand>ner for <persName>Gail</persName>. THen on to the air port. A <transport>two-motor plan</transport>e awaited us(this did not enhance ME) Not many passangers. <hand>We</hand> paid about $6.00over weight- but expected this anyway.About 3/4 hour's flight among the clouds. A bit bumpy. But er GOT ther<hand>e</hand> O.K.</p>
        <p><persName>Mercedes <hand>Bu</hand>cher</persName> met us <misspelling word="at the">atthe</misspelling> Brussels terminal with her new <transport>Ford Sedan</transport>. It <hand>w</hand>as good to see her <hand>!</hand> We always have fun.She drove <hand>to</hand> Brussels and thro the lovely parks. Landing at the <placeName>Metropole</placeName>(where M. Al<hand>s</hand>o lives until her apartment is ready. <hand>W</hand>e <misspelling word="went">wnet</misspelling> up to our rooms. Nothing very fancy but quie<hand>t</hand>. Some flowers arrived from <persName>M.G.</persName> and <persName>Clyde</persName>an d directly <hand>AF</hand>ter,in they came<hand>!</hand>They were at the <placeName><hand>A</hand>lanta hotel</placeName><hand>a</hand>l<hand>m</hand>ost next door on this busy street. We all trailed over to the <u>G<hand>3.R</hand>and</u> <u>Place</u>.Where we had a truly delicious meal of steak <misspelling word="potatoes">p<x>o</x>toes</misspelling> etc on<hand>\</hand>little table placed out<hand>/</hand>on the sidewalk. This beautiful Place is to me one of the most beautifulsig<x>s</x> <hand>I</hand>have ever seen. It is very large and neatly paved with <misspelling word="block">bl<x>f</x><hand>oc</hand>cks</misspelling> of stone- as are most of the streets in <placeName>Brussels</placeName> The distinguished <placeName>Town Hall (Hotel de Ville)</placeName> occupies practi<x>ed</x> <hand>the</hand> end <hand>,</hand> facing the lovely group of<hand>\</hand><placeName>Guild houses</placeName> or <placeName>Corporation Houses</placeName>.All around the square are these very Beautiful struc<hand>tures ,</hand> darkened with age, the carvings and cornices etc <hand>D</hand>ecoratee with gold.The facades are surmount by irregular roofs topped with the emblems of the guilds A baket, a lamb <hand>,</hand> The<hand>|</hand>effect at night, whenthe buildings are wonderfully illu<fade>manated</fade>, is someting never to be forgotten.</p>
        <p>WE drove <hand>with</hand> <persName>M.</persName> in her cosy grey Ford all thro lovely parks.Huge trees, lakes, pleasant <misspelling word="rolling">roll<hand rw="i">o</hand>ng</misspelling> meadows, Flowers in many spots <hand>we</hand> drove past many famous buildings <placeName>Palias de Justice</placeName> etc. After a rest period we set forth again for our <hand>B</hand>eloved  Square where we had a delicious dinner- so g<hand>oo</hand>d and so cheap.In a charming little <misspelling word="resturant">restur  n</misspelling> approached tho' a tiny paved alley. I<hand>N</hand> the <u>Flemish</u> <hand>unSTYLE</hand> carved panels_and old Delft plates pewter and all the brass most <misspelling word="beautiful">beuifully</misspelling> polished. <placeName>Le Bon Vondieux Temps.</placeName> be <u>SUre</u> to visit this if you go to <placeName>Brusssels</placeName>!</p>
    </letter>
    
</xml>