<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml"
	schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>Calendar Entries</title>
            <editor>Rachel Gerzevske</editor>
         </titleStmt>
         <extent>
            Seven total calendar entries that Mary Behrend wrote and/or drew on. 
         </extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <p>COPYRIGHT 1908, BY FRIENDSHIP CALENDAR CO. NEW BRITAIN, CONN.</p>
         </publicationStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <msDesc>
               <msIdentifier><repository>Penn State Erie, The Behrend College Library</repository></msIdentifier>
               <physDesc>
                  <handDesc>
                     <handNote xml:id="redPen" medium="red inkpen">Likely Mary Behrend writing in a red pen.</handNote>
                     <handNote xml:id="blackPen" medium="black inkpen">Likely Mary behrend writing in a black pen.</handNote>
                     <handNote xml:id="calendarPub" medium="print">Text printed onto the page from the calendar manufacturing company.</handNote>
                     
                     <handNote xml:id="pencil" medium="graphite pencil">Text that doesn't look like pen, but is not printed onto the page.</handNote>
                     <handNote xml:id="cutout" medium="printed image">Because the Behrend family is associated with the Hammermill Paper Company, it makes sense that at least one image would be printed from there.</handNote>
                     <handNote xml:id="watercolor" medium="watercolor">A lot of Mary's calendar illustrations appear to be made with watercolor, usually in conjunction with pencils. </handNote>
                  </handDesc>
               </physDesc>
            </msDesc>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text>
      <body>
         <div type="calendarEntries_1">
            <figure>
               <graphic url="https://arrowarchive.github.io/behrendcalendar/photos/july/1909-07-13.jpg"></graphic>
               <fw place="top-center" hand="#calendarPub">COPYRIGHT 1908, BY FRIENDSHIP CALENDAR CO. NEW BRITAIN, CONN.</fw>
               
               <ab hand="#calendarPub"><date>July 13, 1909. Tuesday</date></ab>
               <figDesc>An infant is seen from behind. looking closely, the drawing was made with a different type of paper. It was likely printed, cut out, and glued onto the page.</figDesc>
               <ab hand="#blackPen">That little spot in the back of his neck is the sweetest spot to kiss I know so I kiss him there and <emph style="underline">hold him close</emph> just because I love him so.</ab>
               
               <note>It's clear that Mary is talking about her son Warren here. From the way she talks about him, he is a few months old (or less) and she absolutely adores him. If Warren is her first born child, then her joy from being around him makes a lot more sense. </note>
            </figure>
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>