<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml>
    <title>Guide to People, Places, and Things mentioned in Paul Siple's Letter to Mr. Behrend</title>
    <people>
        <person>
            <name>Ernst Behrend</name>
            <desc>President of the Hammermill Paper Company. Lent a sextant to Paul Siple for use in his Antarctic expedition.</desc>
            <graphic src="photos/Behrend__Ernst.jpg" alt="Ernst Behrend"/>
        </person>
        <person>
            <name>Paul Siple</name>
            <role>Leader/Biologist</role>
            <desc>American Antarctic explorer. Participated in all 5 expeditions conducted by Admiral Byrd.</desc>
            <graphic src="photos/Paulsiple1932.jpg" alt="Paul Siple in 1932"/>
        </person>
        <person>
            <name>Richard Byrd</name>
            <role>Admiral</role>
            <desc>American naval officer and Antarctic explorer. Admiral Byrd conducted 5 Antarctic expeditions between 1928 and 1956.</desc>
            <graphic src="photos/Byrd.jpg" alt="Admiral Richard E Byrd"/>
        </person>
        <person>
            <name>Alton Wade</name>
            <role>Geologist</role>
            <desc>Franklin Alton Wade was an American geologist who accompanied Admiral Richard Byrd on two Antarctic expeditions.</desc>
            <graphic src="photos/Wade.PNG" alt="Franklin Alton Wade"/>
        </person>
        <person>
            <name>Olin Stancliff</name>
            <role>Driver/Assistant</role>
            <desc>Part of Admiral Byrd's Antarctic sledging party. Olin Stancliff primarily served as a dog driver. Little other information is available. No photo could be found.</desc>
        </person>
        <person>
            <name>Stevenson Corey</name>
            <role>Driver/Assistant</role>
            <desc>A supply officer on Admiral Byrd's Antarctic expedition team. He also served as a dog driver along with Olin Stancliff.</desc>
            <graphic src="photos/Corey1933.png" alt="Stevenson Corey in 1933"/>
        </person>
    </people>
    <places>
        <place>
            <name>Marie Byrd Land</name>
            <desc>Unclaimed region of Antarctica. Named after the wife of Admiral Richard E. Byrd.</desc>
            <coords>Coordinates: Between 158°00'W and 103°24'W</coords>
        </place>
        <place>
            <name>Little America</name>
            <desc>A series of bases established in Antarctica by Admiral Byrd.</desc>
            <coords>Coordinates: 78°12′S 162°12′W</coords>
        </place>
        <place>
            <name>Mt. Raymond Fosdick</name>
            <desc>A mountain located in the Fosdick Mountain Range in Marie Byrd Land.</desc>
            <coords>Coordinates: 76°32′S 144°45′W</coords>
        </place>
        <place>
            <name>Edsel Ford Mountain Range</name>
            <desc>The mountain range containing Mt. Raymond Fosdick</desc>
        </place>
    </places>
    <things>
        <thing>
            <name>Sextant</name>
            <desc>An instrument used in celestial navigation used to measure the distance between two visible objects.</desc>
            <graphic src="photos/Sextant.jpg" alt="An image of a sextant"/>
        </thing>
    </things>
</xml>