<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<xml>
    <page>
        <head>
            <p>
                <person>PAUL A. SIPLE</person>
            </p>
            <p>
                <address>1158 WEST FIFTH STREET</address>
            </p>
            <p>
                <city>ERIE, PENNA.</city>
            </p>
            <p>
                <date format="MDY">December 9, 1935</date>
            </p>
        </head>
        <body>
            <greeting>Dear Mr. Behrend,</greeting>
            <p n="1"> It is with great pleasure that I present this little token of friendship. This
                rock was picked up on the "ash dump" - a unique moraine running out from the base of
                an extinct volcano, <location>Mt. Raymond Fosdick</location> in the <location>Edsel
                    Ford Mountain Range</location> of northern <location>Marie Byrd
                    Land,</location> Antarctica. </p>
            <p n="2"> The land was first discovered from the air by <person>Admiral
                    Byrd</person> in <date>1929</date>, but it was first visited by our party
                travelling by dog team during October - December, <date>1934</date>. The Mary Byrd Land
                sledging party was composed of four men - <person>Alton Wade</person>,
                    Geologist,<person>Stevenson Corey</person> and <person>Olin Stancliff</person>,
                drivers and assistants, and myself as leader and Biologist. </p>
            <p n="3"> The volcano was at the extreme turning point of our travels, about three
                hundred miles from <location>Little America</location>. Corey and I spent Thanksgiving Day near the point
                where this rock was picked up in a blizzard that blew almost continuously for three
                days at a velocity rarely below thirty five miles an hour, and often of hurricane
                velocity completely flattening our tent. </p>
            <p n="4"> The sextant you so kindly loaned us helped to <sic>guideus</sic> through the
                hundreds of weary, uncharted miles, and I return it to you with deepest
                appreciation and with it a piece of the Antarctic contintent
                itself. </p>
        </body>
        <foot>
            <p>With kindest regards,</p>
            <p>Sincerely yours,</p>
            <p>Paul A. Siple </p>
            <img src="../pics/Penguin.PNG"/>
        </foot>
    </page>
</xml>
