<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<xml>
    <page>
        <head>
            <person>PAUL A. SIPLE</person>
            <address>1158 WEST FIFTH STREET</address>
            <city format="city,state">ERIE, PENNA.</city>
            <date format="MDY">December 9, 1935</date>
        </head>
        <body>
            <greeting>Dear Mr. Behrend,</greeting>
            <paragraph n="1"> It is with great pleasure that I present this little token of
                friendship. This rock was picked up on the "ash dump" - a unique moraine running out
                from the base of an extinct valcano, <location>Mt. Raymound Fosdick in the Edsel
                    Ford Mountain Range of northern Marie Byrd Land,</location> Antartica. </paragraph>
            <paragraph n="2"> The land was first discovered from the air by <person>Admiral
                    Byrd</person><date> in 1929,</date> but it was first visited by our party
                traveling by dog team during October December, <date>1934.</date> The Mary Byrd Land
                sledging party was composed of four men - <teamMembers num="5"><person>Alton Wade,
                        Geologist,</person><person>Stevenson Corey</person> and <person>Olin
                        Stancliff</person>, drivers and assistants, and <person>myself</person> as
                    leader and Biologist.</teamMembers>
            </paragraph>
            <paragraph n="3"> The volcano was at the extreme turn-ing point of our travels,
                    <distance>about three hun-dred miles from Little America</distance>.
                    <person>Corey</person> and I spent Thanksgiving Day near the point where this
                rock was picked up in a blizzard that blew almost continuosly for three days at a
                velocity rarely below thirty five miles an hour, and often of hurricane velocity
                completely flattening our tent. </paragraph>
            <paragraph n="4">
                <equipment>The sextant</equipment>you so kindly loaned us helped to guideus through
                the hundreds of weary, uncharted miles, and I returned it to you with deepest
                appreciation and with it a piece of <location>Antarctic contintent</location>
                itself. </paragraph>
        </body>
        <space/>
        <closing line="1">With kindest regards,</closing>
        <closing line="2">Sincerly yours,</closing>
        <sign type="handwritten">Paul A. Siple </sign>
        <graphic src="../pics/Penguin.PNG"/>
    </page>
</xml>
