<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<xml>
    <letter>
        <handWritten>
            <underLine><date>Sunday</date>. To<place>Brugus</place>-</underLine> milt mercedes clee
            arlsoas </handWritten>
        <typeWrite>
            <p n="1">THIS was a DAY<handWwritten>!</handWwritten>
                <person>M.G.</person> and <people>Clyde</people> plus <people>Cail</people> and
                myself all in <transPort>Mercedes' Ford</transPort>, travelled over theMotor
                Highway. First lookked up the <place>Flea Market</place> which was just next to
                nothing Then on to <place>Burges</place>.passing culticated fields and neat little
                    houses.<handWritten>M</handWritten>. drove us all around by the canals etc. A
                truly wonderful and unspoiled little city of the past. Got a Victoria with a
                    <animal>horse</animal> named Bella. A very FAT <animal>horse</animal> but she
                didn't have to go very fast.M.G. got very conversational with Bella owner. IN
                    <language>French</language> . Visited enclosdure of the <place>Beguinage</place>
                and the <place>chapel</place> where the sisters of the nursing order were chanting.
                Being <day>sunday</day> almost all the shops were closed. But we saw the women
                making t the bobbin lace and bought a few pieces. The buildings around the enclosure
                called the <place>Beguinage</place> were used in olden times
                    for<handWritten>|</handWritten>wives and widows, and women of some stand
                ing-when the men were at war or had been killed etc. We had <meal>dinner</meal> in
                    <place>Brussels</place> again on our beloved Place- the large square. The
                building with the electric lights well placed were marvelous. We hated to
                    leave<drawing>goes in this spot</drawing>it. </p></typeWrite>
        <drawing writting="underneith">The owners if "Bella" (the
            <underline>horse</underline>)</drawing>
        <drawing>horse and carrage with clyde</drawing> The Square is a breath taking spot The
        buildings surrounding it are rather <culture>Dutch</culture> or <culture>Flemish</culture> in <x word="stay">srcibble</x>
        style. The tips of the irregulad
        roofs being surmounted by the emblems of the various Guilds- as many of the buildings
        were old Guild Houses.The buildings are darkwith age 
        and carveo richly and ornamented with gold. Further 
        embelished with gold paint<handWritten>|</handWritten>on the sills and carvinngs.
        the llights on the buildings at night create a truly 
        neautiful and unreal effect. Like part|of a fairy tale 
            M.G. and Clyde have been with us three day and
        we have all,had one grand time.
    </letter>
</xml>
