<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="RelaxNGforThetravelProjects/Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
    <!--images you're working with: which ones are page images and which ones are photos?
  Consider moving these so they sit with the parts of the transcription they connect to.
  -->

  <!--  <graphic url="images/IMG_7189.jpg" alt="rat"/>


    <graphic url="images/IMG_7191.jpg" alt="france_adventure"/>


    <graphic url="images/IMG_7193.jpg" alt="France_hot"/>


    <graphic url="images/IMG_7200.jpg" alt="big castle"/>-->
    <!-- MOVE and integrate these images with the transcript. -->

<letter>   
     <figure>
        <graphic url="images/July19.jpg"/>
        <caption>July 19th letter</caption>
    </figure>
    <!-- FIRST IMAGE TRANSCRIPT: -->
    <dateLine>
        <placeName>Paris</placeName>
        <date when="1955-07-19">July 19th. <hand>1955</hand></date>
    </dateLine>
   
    <p n="1">Took a <transport>motor</transport> from<fade>a</fade> travel agency- after <meal>breakfast</meal> in our fancy round sitting room. Drove all around <placeName>Paris</placeName> the driver named <persName>Harvey</persName> had a daughter named <eSpace>-</eSpace>  at <placeName>Waycross Georgia</placeName>. <eSpace>-</eSpace> Went to 
        <placeName>Lubin's</placeName> for <misspelling word="perfume">perfrume</misspelling> (had the <item>pink flannel</item> <misspelling word="affair">faffair</misspelling> that <persName>Harriet</persName> had given me—REsented') Walked around the circle—<placeName>Place de Vendome</placeName> to
            <placeName>Caron</placeName>, <placeName>The Ritz Hotel</placeName>, and a <placeName>Jewellers</placeName>
        where I was intregued by a <item>Jewelled bird</item>. But did NOT get it! To a very nice resturant in
        the <placeName>Bois</placeName> for <meal>lunch</meal> <placeName>Le Pre Catalan</placeName>. Went then to both sides of the <placeName>Sien</placeName> and got some little
        <item>prints</item> of <placeName>Paris</placeName>. <placeName>R.R. station</placeName> and <placeName>Tourist Agency<hand>|</hand>reg</placeName>. <item>tickets</item>. <eSpace>-</eSpace> We had our evening meal at the
        <placeName>Bristol</placeName> and then set out for the <placeName>Casion deParis</placeName>. Very amusing show- we stayed thro<hand>'</hand>
            <u>half</u> of it but felt we needed <u>sleep</u>. <persName>Gail</persName> got a <transport>cab</transport> by her shrill <eSpace>-</eSpace>
            <u>whistle</u>!"</p>

    <!-- Add in the <graphic/> element for this page? -->

    <p n="2"><!-- SECOND IMAGE TRANSCRIPT: --> <hand><item>STATUE</item> IN THE <persName>DAVIDSON'S</persName> <placeName>GARDEN</placeName></hand>, <hand>PICNIC IN THE
        FORREST</hand>.</p>
</letter>
    
 <letter>   
     <figure>
         <graphic url="images/July26.jpg"/>
         <caption>July 26th letter</caption>
     </figure>
    <!-- Is this a new letter? DO YOU WANT A NEW FILE FOR EACH LETTER?   -->
    <dateLine><date when="1955-07-26">July 26, 1955</date></dateLine><p n="3"><!-- THIRD IMAGE TRANSCRIPT: -->  <placeName>Brussles</placeName> - Dear People: We are just about to
        take off for <placeName>Copenhagen</placeName> and are sit-ting around so I will try to send this second
        intallement of our trip report. If I remember correctly, the last letter came from the <transport>boat</transport>.
        We arrived in <placeName>Cherbourg</placeName> and got safely on the <transport>train</transport> to find that it was over 90. We nearly
        died on the ride to <placeName>Paris</placeName>. Very unairconditioned <transport>train</transport> and blazing sun. The first thing we
        did when we arrived at <placeName>Le Bristol</placeName> was fall in a cold tub. WE went out for <meal>dinner</meal> later and
        cele-brated with Cherrie Jubilee. Very Tasty! The next day <persName>Mrs. Behrend</persName> hired a car and
        guide and we drove all over <placeName>Paris</placeName>. It is so beautiful but so expensive? $90 a minute to
        breath! We did a bit of shopping, had <meal>lunch</meal> in the <placeName>Bois de Boulougne</placeName> shopped on the <placeName>Left
        Bank</placeName>, got <transport>train</transport> <item>tickets</item> and that night went to the <placeName>Casino de Paris</placeName>. Pretty naked ladies I
        must say. We were not carried away by it but see it, so that is that. The next morning we
        were up at the crack of dawn and off to Tours. the man and his wife who ran the <placeName>Manior
        Bercheron</placeName>, where we stayed as a member of the family were terribly nice. We arrived in time
        for <meal>lunch</meal> and got in a little <transport>car</transport> and went through some beautiful country to see some of the
        <placeName>chateaux</placeName>. We enjoyed it tremendously. You can see where all the old French painters got all
        their inspirations. Lovely rivers, old mills and beautiful trees. That night after <meal>dinner</meal> we
        went to a nearby <placeName>chateau</placeName>, <placeName>Azay-le-Rideau</placeName> which was illuminated. Just like <placeName>fairyland</placeName>. They
        also had a sort of play very cleverly done just done with voices and lighting which told the
        history of the <placeName>building</placeName>. We will never forget it. Thursday, the <persName>Davidsons</persName>, our hosts and
        their little boy and ourselves went on another <placeName>chateaux</placeName> trip which was just a grand as the
        day before. We had a picnic on the way and tea on the way home. Great fun. The only thing
        that marred the trip was another guest who arrived who knew all about everything and told it
        in the loudest of voices. I got in a ter-rible row with him about sports. Everyone was on my
        side but you couldn't get a word in edge wise. It was was rather funny to look back on but I
        nearly had a nervous breakdown when it was going on. Friday we left Tours at about eleven
        and got back in <placeName>Paris</placeName> for <meal>lunch</meal>. After the lovely meal we charged out on foot to do some
        shopping. </p>
     

       <p n="4"><!-- FOURTH IMAGE TRANSCRIPT: --> <hand><placeName>AZAY-LE-RIDEAU</placeName></hand></p>
   </letter>
</xml>
