<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="file:////udrive.ad.psu.edu/users/n/p/npv4/My%20Documents/frontandbackrng4.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
    <front>
        <meta>Correct copy P. J. Long COPY Hammermill Paper Company</meta>
        
        <paragraph n="1">
            <p>On December 19th, 1929 Warren Behrend on his way to join his family </p>
            <p>for the christmas holiday met a school bus at this place. The bus Made a left</p>
            <p>turn in front of his car without giving the proper signal. Instantly this </p>
            <p>man decided to run his car off the road bed, though it was slippery, to save these</p>
            <p>children. his car overturned in this effort, killing him instantly </p>
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph n="2">
            <p>in my experience, I have never known a finer example of self forget-</p>
            <p>fulness, esteeming the safety of others before oneself. Had he hesitated but</p>
            <p>an instant the tragedy of that fatal day would have been written in deeper lines</p>
            <p>some who are here today in possession of youthful health would almost certainly</p>
            <p>have suffered with him.</p>
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph n="3">
            <p>it is appropriate to this occasion that young people of this</p>
            <p>community pause today to consider his wonderful example of heroic sacrifice.</p>
            <p>Warren's deed is a compelling challenge to every one present, most definitely to </p>
            <p>every boy and girl in this community to dedicate ourselves to the call of duty </p>
            <p>andof unselfish service. This deed should, and i confidently trust, will be </p>
            <p>an inspiration to succeeding generations to respond instantly to the call to</p>
            <p>duty even though it may mean to sacrifice.</p>
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph n="4">
            <p>As you young people look out into the world today the call to </p>
            <p>unselfish service was never so compelling. Many of the finer things of life are </p>
            <p>in peril. It is confused, almost hysterical. There is no remedy on earth for </p>
            <p>these disorders so effectual as deeds not words of kindess, of self forgetfulness,</p>
            <p>and unselfish sacrifice. May we not treasure Warren's heroic deed enacted in our</p>
            <p>midst as a reminder to all future generations that the highest duty is always to </p>
            <p>others rather than to ourselves.</p>
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph n="5">
            <p>This community, the two schools in this immediate neighborhood and </p>
            <p>more particularly the children whose lives were saved by warren Behrend's heroism,</p>
            <p>with their parents and friends come today to pay respectful tribute to his wonderful</p>
        </paragraph>
    </front>
    <back>
        <meta>COPY HAMMERMILL PAPER COMPANY</meta>
        
        <paragraph n="5 ">
            <p>life crowded as it was with all the rich promise of a most useful and happy</p>
            <p>career, then suddenly ccrowned by sacrificing all to the safety of children,</p>
            <p>though the children themselves were unkown to him.</p>
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph n="6">
            <p>If inspired by the sacrifice of this splendid young man, you</p>
            <p>boys and girls will dedicate your lives to the great tasks of life, not</p>
            <p>sparing yourselves but givingg youselves instantly and cheerfully when duty </p>
            <p>calls, then the beautiful example of this splendid young man will not have </p>
            <p>been in vein.</p>
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph n="7">
            <p>From what we learn of his exalted character we think that we</p>
            <p>would wish nothing better tan that these children spared by his heroic</p>
            <p>decision should contribute something worth while to make the world better.</p>
        </paragraph>
    </back>
</xml>

